Guide to the Abraham Aronow Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits and Views Acquired in 2017, 1982-2017; Series V; 0.46 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Portraits on Photographic Prints, 11 x 14 inches
    - Rapoport, Sonya, 1923-2015, printed on 2012 October 31; portrait created 2012 July 6 (Box 26, Folder 671)
      Rapoport at her home in Berkeley, California
    - Reed, Eli, 1946-, printed on 2013 April 2; portrait created 2003 September 12 (Box 26, Folder 672)
      Reed is a photographer
      Reed at Magnum Photos in New York City
    - Samuelson, Paul A. (Paul Anthony), 1915-2009, printed on 2014 September 25; portrait created 1984 July 2 (Box 26, Folder 673)
      Samuelson was an economist, author and recipient of the Nobel Prize in Economic Sciences in 1970
      Samuelson in his office at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology in Cambridge, Massachusetts
    - Seaborg, Glenn T. (Glenn Theodore), 1912-1999, printed on 2014 November 9; portrait created 1983 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 674)
      Seaborg was a chemist and recipient of the Nobel Prize in Chemistry in 1951
      Seaborg in his office at the University of California, Berkeley, in Berkeley, California
    - Shulman, Julius, 1910-2009, printed on 2012 April 4; portrait created 2004 May 16 (Box 26, Folder 675)
      Shulman was an architectural photographer
      Shulman at his home in Laurel Canyon, Los Angeles, California
    - Skinner, B.F. (Burrhus Frederic), 1904-1990, printed on 2014 September 5; portrait created 1984 July 2 (Box 26, Folder 676)
      Skinner was a psychologist and author
      Skinner at his home in Cambridge, Massachusetts
    - Soth, Alec, 1969-, printed on 2013 March 29; portrait created 2007 August 20 (Box 26, Folder 677)
      Soth is a photographer
      Soth at the San Francisco Art Institute in San Francisco
    - Stegner, Wallace, 1909-1993, printed on 2012 March 16; portrait created 1984 February 22 (Box 26, Folder 678)
      Stegner was an author, environmentalist, and historian
      Stegner at his home in Los Altos Hills, California
    - Sterling, Joseph, 1935-2010, printed on 2013 March 25; portrait created 2007 December 18 (Box 26, Folder 679)
      Sterling was a photographer
      Sterling in San Francisco, California
    - Stock, Dennis, 1928-2010, printed on 2013 April 2; portrait created 2003 September 12 (Box 26, Folder 680)
      Stock was a photographer
      Stock at his home in Essex, Connecticut
    - Stone, Erika, 1924-, printed on 2012 July 10; portrait created 2002 August 8 (Box 26, Folder 681)
      Stone is a photographer
      Stone at her him in New York City
    - Tress, Arthur, 1940-, printed on 2012 April 10; portrait created 2011 October 29 (Box 26, Folder 682)
      Tress is a photographer
      Tress at the Center for Creative Photography at the University of Arizona in Tucson, Arizona
    - Unidentified man at breakfast at the cafe of Bruno's Country Club in Gerlach, Nevada, printed on 2002 June 23; portrait created 2002 June 16 (Box 26, Folder 683)
  - Views on Photographic Prints, 11 x 14 inches
    Views on selenium toned black and white silver gelatin prints.
    Arranged chronologically by image creation date
    - Detail, Pipeline Apparatus, Pumping Station, Owens River Gorge, California, printed on 2012 May 14; images created 1992 May 17; 2 photographic prints (Box 26, Folder 684)
    - Owens Lake, Owens Valley, California, printed on 2012 May 14; image created 1996 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 685)
    - Detail, Partially Restored Interior, Cerro Gordo Ghost Town, overlooking Owens Lake, California, printed on 2012 April 12; image created 1996 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 686)
    - Re-creation of Wild Bill Hickcock's Ultimate Hand, Partially Restored Interior, Cerro Gordo Ghost Town, overlooking Owens Lake, California, printed on 2012 April 12; image created 1996 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 687)
    - Ruins of Beehive Charcoal Kiln, on shore of Owens Lake, California, printed on 2012 May 16; image created 1996 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 688)
    - Ranger Reed, A Lone Life's Journey Into Naught, Edgehill Studio, San Francisco, California, printed on 2009 November 17; image created 2009 October 10 (Box 26, Folder 689)